xtremepicks.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy Policy : Xtremepicks | Penny Stock Alerts | Penny Stocks | Penny Stock Picks | Best Penny Stocks | Hot Penny Stocks

This policy covers how Xtremepicks.com treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Collection and Use**

Xtremepicks.com collects personal information when you register with Xtremepicks.com.

Xtremepicks.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.

Xtremepicks.com uses information for the following general purposes: to personalize the content you see, fulfill your requests, contact you, and to improve our services.

**Information Sharing**

Xtremepicks.com DOES NOT RENT, SELL, OR SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

• We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

• We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Xtremepicks.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

• We transfer information about you if Xtremepicks.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Xtremepicks.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Confidentiality**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**Cookies**

We may place a cookie on your personal computer. A cookie is a small computer file that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. Cookies help us recognize you when you visit our site again. We use cookies on our site to collect session data for several purposes to personalize and improve your individual viewing experiences on our site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Xtremepicks.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Xtremepicks.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
